What is the expectation from us
and what is our expectation from you,
we will know this in this, before that we should do this
that you should tell people, it is important to tell
because we will not be able to know how many
people are there, whether
you have the knowledge of this or not, have you
people got the basic knowledge of insurance, have you been
trained before,
yes
sir Saroj
ji, in basic what is OD, what is TP, all these
things have been told to you, yes
sir,
all the
people, please
tell this Vikas ji,
you all know everything, all these things have been told
Sachin Kumar Yadav, District
Darbhanga, yes sir, it has been told
and there is anything else that you want to know, yes
sir, whatever process is there beyond this, please tell us,
okay
and who are the other people,
all of you please reply in the chat box, have
you got the basic information of insurance, if you have not got it, then no, if you have got it, then yes, it is
okay because without it the work will not be done
Devraj
ji, you can unmute your audio
Gaurav Kumar
Muzaffarpur Gunjan Kumar
Purnia Kunal Singh
One  Bye one you guys please tell Manu Tiwari
Darbhanga Raja Babu Darbhanga you guys are getting
everyone's messages in the basic chat box
sir the training coming in the chat box has been
given very well sir
tuts really nice it is good so
this is done what have
you guys been told till now about the work that you have to do so far
what have you guys been told so far
can someone unmute and tell me
hello ha ha tell me yes sir ji hello hello sir
this is though we have to get the
training
about two wheeler insurance i.e. insurance and information about how to do what not to do
we are
going very
good and how to do this the
information is not confirmed yet the
amount will be there so sir told you all the
system means you guys will get it till the training
Vinod ji have I
received it till now hello
yes training training basic training is
completed the basic training of the driver
means basic training means I partner p yasap
what is the basic of
insurance who should get insurance
what are the benefits of insurance  What are the disadvantages of not having it,
all that has become basic. Then the
portal
ID and password have been provided to the I-Partners. After
entering your password ID, then
how will the training of that I-Partner be done, how will the
policy be third party, how will it be
OD and how will the COMP be,
how will the package policy be
complete, they have been given information.
Apart from this, they were told what is PA cover, what is
PA cover, as well as about add-on cover,
like Zero Dep, the entire one day
session was about add-on cover, so add-on cover was
also explained to them in detail, it will
not be clear to everyone in I-Main, but
training has been given once, then
after that, what are the
processes of claim, either what
things do we have to keep in mind while taking the policy
or what things do they have to keep in mind while making the policy
so that
wrong policy is not made, all those basic things have been
trained. Rest, what is to be done now,
how to do it, they have been told that
you have to coordinate
with the police
or traffic police at your checkpoints at the intersections in any area.  You have to do
business, you have to participate in the arrest campaigns
that are run, you have to do
business on your own, you have to go out in the field, there are
many such
ideas, all these things were trained by Dharmesh Sir,
yes sir, okay,
you guys must have
some expectations in this project, that is,
we have received this training, so what,
how and where will we have to do, right now if
you want you can tell,
if any of you want, please unmute and tell, sir, I
would like to tell you about insurance,
Amit ji sir, can my voice reach me, can I hear
your voice at all,
sir, when insurance is made, there is
first party, second and third, so the
first party sir, the owner of the car becomes the
first party and the second party sir, is the
company
and in the third party sir, first
complete the first party, after that
come to the third, there is no need for that, Amit
ji, we want to know what your own
expectations are, what do you think
how this will work, do you understand it or
not, we want to know sir, do you
understand it now  So far, we have
n't been able to get that much information, and sir, we were away from the LAT,
so we might not have been able to get it. We have undergone training,
but we haven't been able to get that much information.
We are associated with the LAT. Sir, you guys have
learned about insurance,
but it's important to know how we will
source business. Yes, sir, so far there are
two scenarios. One is that you have received the
ID and password, so
after that you can source business yourself. The
second is
that Dharmesh ji and Vinod ji will do
government liaisoning.
After liaisoning, wherever there will be vehicle
checking, you can facilitate them and
explain to them that this is
how we do insurance. The
advantage of this is that you will be
fined Rs 5,000. Your work will be done in 1,000 days. If
you explain all this to them and get it done,
you can source business there. There are
two ways, one is attachment with the
government, and the other is that you
can do it individually as well; there are no limitations in that.
Yours is that you can do it only when you are attached to the group
or you can do it anywhere without the government
and like
next time
Dharmesh ji is going to come to Bihar, so he will tell
you how to do it after talking to the government,
how to do liaisoning, in which
areas to
meet the Superintendent of Police and
how they will do it, he will give you all this information, so whatever
profit you have to make in it, whether it is
through the government or without the
government, this was one point about
how to source the business, okay,
you people must have been told about ICICI Lombard,
you can unmute in between and
tell me, you know, don't know,
what is it about,
hello sir,
I am Gunjan speaking, sir, speak from Punia,
Gunjan ji was
speaking about ICC Lomat, so we have
n't given that much basic information, we haven't
told you how to do it, we haven't given you basic information about it,
I will give you
a recap  ICC Labad
Insurance Company is the second largest
insurance company in general insurance
and the largest company in private sector.
You are currently associated here through ICICI Labad,
so its main purpose is to
drive the State Insurance Plan.
Whatever work is related to the government in the State Insurance Plan has to be
driven through it.
And even without the government, if you
do it anywhere, then we will provide the
support you need. So this is about ICICI Labad
and I request you all to
go today and
do a little research on how it works, how does
insurance work, what are its
benefits, how does ICICI Labad work,
what kind of company is ICC Labad, do a
little bit of this from your end, it is a big
brand, you will get its benefit in the
market. Secondly, what will be
your
benefits within the company, what benefits will you get,
how will you get it? Dharam Sir
or Vinod ji must have given you all this information.
If not, then please
talk to them and get it from them.  Yes, okay
sir,
okay, we will come now. The
form which Vinod ji has shared with you, okay, in that, definitely
put your name, district name, and in the near about, the place where you want to go, and phone number etc. After this, Vinod ji will share it with me, you will be
allocated by calling you accordingly.
Here you will
see Sachin Singh ji with us. He looks after the entire Koshi
belt and
also looks after all the districts of Motihari, Bettiah, Shivhar. The
biggest location
of the district is near Sachin ji.
Sachin ji, if you want to tell something about yourself,
then please add two lines.
Good afternoon to everyone, I am Sachin Singh. I look after
you Purnia location and the entire Motihari
location. If you
need any kind of help from us, then
I am always there for you. So, if anyone from this has any information about
his Purnia location or Motihari
location, the districts in Purnia, and those from
Purnia, Madhepura, Saharsa, Munger etc. are
here, and the location which is from Motihari, then
you will get it in Motihari.
Motihari, Bettiah and Gopalganj, you have Shivan,
then Sitamari, Shivhar, so it
seems Shashi ji's voice got disconnected,
anyway I will leave two questions for you guys,
okay, what is the
role of the broker in this work, what is the
role of the PMP where you are working, you
guys find out what is there in it and the second question is
what support do you need from us, right now the
support system that I have is that
if you face any
problem in making your insurance or if there is a
technical glitch, payment has been made
but the policy is not generated, then we
can raise that thing and solve it,
okay, but if there is all these other work
like which location and where will you stay,
Vinod ji and Dharmesh ji will tell you,
how will the liaisoning with the police be done,
how to work with the police, they will also tell you all these things,
so these two things should be clarified
in your mind, what do you want from yourself, what do
you want from the company
Where will we and the support of ICICI Labad be deployed in it, okay, so there are many
things that we will do,
Roshan ji is probably asking
what will be the benefit of this, you are
asking the benefit of which thing, Roshan
ji can unmute, Roshan ji can
unmute,
Naveen Shah ji, you also have a hand raise, you
can also unmute, if there is anything then
yes sir, yes tell me, Naveen ji am listening,
yes sir, I was saying that
I am from Jammu district,
yes I am listening, tell me on
what basis will we do this, will we have to
coordinate with the administration and get it done,
you asked a very correct question, you asked a very correct
question, I wanted to hear
this, this question should
come to everyone's mind, yes sir, if we will
coordinate with the administrative officer, then
how will we do it, the
whole and soul training
or the liaisoning,
meeting with the senior officers, Dharmesh sir will do it on
his own basis and will tell you people,
some people will also do this and will
tell you people, okay, if needed,
yours  If you have Dharmesh Sir's number, then
take it from Vinod Ji. Call Vinod Ji.
How will we go to which location, Sir? I
mean, how will we go there? You do
n't have such authority until you talk to the police
and you won't be able to deal with those things there. So, you have to discuss
those things
once. You have to discuss them internally and then go there.
Talk to him before there is any problem, Sir, because the
police station which is one kilometer
away from my house, the
police
administration and
even the officials
cannot do any work like this. Personally,
until your Dharmesh Sir comes and
liaises with all the things, then in the
meantime, you can start working on your own. You can write the
insurance for those who are not insured in your account, you
can get it made in that account. Till then,
we have given everyone a tool called
E M Parivahan. In that,
I have told them that whatever
vehicle you put in front of you, check the number of that vehicle,
leave the one which is insured and
talk to the one which is not insured,
because it has to be done.  This would have been the biggest question,
so till the time Sir is not coming to you
or we are not reaching you, I
think we will meet you by 7th date, so till 7th date,
what should you do, individually
because you will have to learn this thing,
how to take out a quote, how to make a policy,
we have given you training once or twice, you can make
two, four, five policies daily in your vicinity, they will be done,
then after that when we come,
then you people will get connected to the
facilities and services available at your local level, it will be easier for you,
but one more thing to keep in mind is that to
become an expert, your hands should be completely
fast, it is not that it
takes an hour to make a policy, yes Sir,
a policy should be made within a minute or two, you will be able to do it only
when you issue a quote daily, it will create
more traffic jam than that, you
just have to continue your practical,
Sir, you have to do it yourself, some
people had to do their
ID and password, some people have
not received it, so there is no need to worry about that,
I have shared the area wise
ID and password with Vinod ji  He will
create all his IDs and do whatever you want,
you can call him, send a message
that this is my location, for this
sir, please create an ID password with this name,
he will create it and give it to you, understood?
And one person had a question that will the ID
password that you get remain for life time?
Yes, it remains for life time,
but if there is any payment
pending in it or it is not used for a long time, then
its password expires, so
he will have to keep using it from time to time,
okay, and if you have any question then
please tell me,
whatever question you have, you can put your question, you can
clear your doubts, you can get answers to your questions
because only when you are clear, the
business will be able to work well, so do
not keep any doubt in your mind, please
tell me whatever is there, every question will be answered,
Surendra
ji, please message slowly because if you
put everything in the chat box at once, it will
not be understood, do a hand race, you could have
taken it two by one  Let's take people along, your
questions may help more people,
if someone has a question that sir
how will we earn income, sir Vinod ji will give you the right answer to this,
Vinod ji please
address this a little bit for this
because right now sir
we have to do that all the people who are going to work in this, by
whatever means, should
clear that once, you have time till this date,
everything will be clear on this date
because once it comes to you, the benefit of whatever
business you
do, we are
talking to your NCC team Udaan, so whatever both the things are cleared,
after that we will clear it for you
sir, how will the salary be in this, there
is no salary, Ayush Raj ji, this is a big work, so if
you do it well then you will get
more than the salary, if you don't do it then it won't
come at all, sir there is a possibility of earning not much but very
much in this,
we had discussed that thing once with you in the training
also a model was told to you people as to how much
incentive is there in the work and there will be no salary in it, in
fact if you work then it will be more than the salary
but  It is not a salary based job,
it will come to you as per your convenience,
okay,
and these people are coming on certain dates, so
accordingly,
you people will be given a target as to
how to do it,
how much we have to do in the three months of January, February and March, it will be communicated to
you once by Vinod ji or
Dharmesh ji, okay, and if you
need any support from my end,
please tell me, Gunjan Kumar ji from Purnia, you
raised your hand, please
say, hello
sir, hello, yes, can you hear me, Gunjan ji,
please tell me, sir, I was saying, today in the
morning we met a person,
we were checking after taking his vehicle number, then he asked us, will
you issue a challan, we
told him, no, no, no, we are checking like this,
I do not have the ID password right now,
so we were checking with another pop,
okay, see what is this, see,
this is an awkward situation, it can also be wrong,
some people may say, why are you checking, is he a
thief, what, there are many kinds of things for
him.  You have to do this by taking it on faith that till when
is your vehicle insured, is it
insured or not, should
I check and tell you, you have to do it after
checking, either the police
is there then you can do it, okay, or you
can do it by taking the customer into confidence,
okay, and if you do it like this then he will think brother this is
my car, what does it mean,
Chandan Shah ji
please tell me,
hello Prem sir, yes tell me sir, we do
n't have traffic police here,
who ca
n't it be, in which
DI Jammula, there is
no traffic police, sir, it is the local police
station in Balok Bagar,
we are there, can it be there,
sir,
mute the rest of the people,
please be a little gentleman,
his voice is coming from behind, please
mute it
[music], you
can do it there also, but the
same thing is that once you have liaison with the police,
then you can do it, Chan ji, sir, so sir,
can we line up, sir, line up means you are asking,
telling me, means sir, we are asking, sir, we are
asking, so right now line up
No, you will come on 7th, what is his name,
Dharmesh ji, Vinod ji will come here, they will
line you all up,
after that you
can proceed with that work, till then one
more thing can be done in this, Sir, at your
level also, if you know, know,
befriend, then you can talk to them and
work with them on your own, the
rest we will come and it will become easier, you
can do it in two ways, Chandan ji, one is you can do it
from the police, one is you
can do it without it also, suppose someone's
car is not insured, okay,
you have the ID password, then you
can get it insured for me, one
way is this, okay, the second way is that once you get the
filing from the police, then
after that this will be done,
thank you, Sir Surendra Kumar Rajak ji,
please
tell me,
a GI has his own revenue, in that he has
taken 5 percent in the cost, okay, Surendra
Kumar Rajak ji's app is there, can you
ask for some reduction in the cost of the car, I have a car,
okay then  What will have to be done if someone else has taken the papers of the vehicle,
see if someone else has taken the car of another person, then the
name will have to be transferred to him, the
most important thing in making insurance
is
RC,
yes tell me it is, your voice is getting cut, sir is not giving the papers, we cannot do anything for that, we will not fight for you, next if anyone else wants to ask something please [music] okay okay okay, what if I am showing it, yes Naveen ji, please tell me, yes sir I was asking sir, I had one more
question, sir, like as of today,
about Jammu district,
10 per cent people have licenses,
90 per cent people do not live there, so will there be
some procedure for them too, sir,
because many such friends are saying that
you can do IRSA, see I understood your
question, you can do IRSA,
but he will not get the claim if
he does not have the license, yes he will not get the claim, either
he should show that the person who has the
license was driving, okay, if the license is
not there then the claim will not be given, whether it is
Jamui or Patna or Delhi  Yes, there are
many friends who are asking that
okay sir, you are issuing insurance
but many such people do not have a license,
so
put your point across if any option comes to mind,
if you are prepared for the license then we can
apply for the insurance license also,
if you can get it done by meeting someone then it is a
different matter, so here it is
not possible in this firm, so Naveen ji, for this you
do one thing, whatever such people there are in the RTO who get the
work done,
you talk to them and get it done from here,
this is in L, this is in L, Naveen ji,
without a license you will not
get any claim, okay,
like people ask for insurance, that means if you get it done, if you do not have a
license then you will not get any
claim, yes that is there, you will not get that, you will not get that,
okay sir it is clear, okay, you will have to
talk to some RPO person,
yes Subodh Subodh ji from Purnia is asking
how to contact the police station, so
Subodh ji, let me tell you that for
contacting the police station, Dharmesh ji, Dharmesh
ji  He will come and his liaisoning will be done there. We will
first talk to the SP and then it will be done
with the police station. Okay, Subo ji's answer is done. Will
we get ID card and
letter from the state government or
not? Thank you sir. Okay sir. Okay.
Sunil Kumar ji is asking whether we will get
ID card or government letter
or not. Your company has received the government letter. The
PMP broker has received its letter
and according to that, they will do the liaisoning and
introduce you all. They will get you all
identified that brother, this
man of ours will be staying here and will issue insurance,
so you will not have any problem with that. And
even if you go with that letter, he will
not weigh that much and your weight will not increase that much.
So, let your seniors do this work, it will be better.
Okay, next,
okay, once everything is sorted out, the next
question is,
sir,
who will decide the area of ​​work?
Area. You have two things, one your
preference will be seen and second the company will decide
where you are working, in which place
you will be posted.  It is being preferred, we will do it there and it will
depend on who is doing well, this was
Niti Kumar Shah ji's question, right, what else  It
seems everything has been deleted, is
n't it? Sir, can one or two people do it? Yes,
yes, it can definitely be done,
and it will be needed too. If there is a busy
intersection, one person will not be able to do it, there will be a
jam, more people will be
needed there. Yes, Sir, that is your company,
PMP Broker, it will tell you,
which people will stay where? You do
n't have to worry about that. You have to focus on your training and
increasing your knowledge. Okay, yes
Sir, the next question is, can we do it? I have
not received your ID password.
Your ID password will be available to you. Mr. Tiwari
from Darbhanga will give it to you. Vinod
ji's ID password, okay, you can contact us for this
and
you will get it. Second, Sir, we have already told you what benefits we will get.
Sir, when will we get the salary in this? We will
not get the salary. We have also told you
how the income will be. The more business you do, the more
income
you will get. The more business you will have, the more
income you will get in the broking business. It can be more than your salary.
In this, you must be seeing a number for Purnia and Motihari.
Sachin ji, please
note down everything and
say.  So I will tell you that I have to do it,
what are you saying, we
can do more than that,
no, there is no limit to this, we can do as much as we can,
sir, one more thing, sir, we have not received the letter,
from which letter we
will also get it, you will get the letter, there is a link
of the I-partner,
you will get it, sir,
do one thing, sir, complete the meeting now, then
you people should not leave anything, right now
I will tell everyone how to link the ID, password and how the
policy will be made,
I will give you training once again, okay sir,
okay, and Nan ji, tell me, you raised your hand, yes
sir, it will be done, a group will be created location wise,
okay
sir, there is already a group,
location wise group, yes, there is a district wise
group, but once it gets
cleared, then we will add you people
to that group, right now
some ins and outs are happening in it, right, so as soon as it gets
cleared, after that date,
then we will give you the letter, you people
must maintain clarity on how to do it, what will happen,
as some people are asking questions,
asking questions is very important.  To know the answer, there is a
message from [ __ ], how will the work be done without meeting you, you
can meet me, it is not a big deal,
I sit in Muzaffarpur branch
or sometimes I stay in Patna branch, like
today I am in Patna branch, so you can meet me, it is
not a big deal, where do you sit,
what was his name,
right Anshu Chaudhary ji, where do you sit, if you
want, you can meet me
in Muzaffarpur, I have also told you on the
call, when we spoke yesterday, whom did you speak to yesterday,
a minute, yesterday I spoke to someone in Muzaffarpur,
tell me, it must have been Pankaj or Sudhanshu, yes, when I
spoke to Sudhanshu, I had only
told him the address, you can meet there, there is
no issue, there is no issue in meeting at all, if you have any
question or any query, you
can send it to me, there is no
problem for that, okay, and what else did you have any other
question, Naveen ji, do you have any other question,
your hand
is raised, the question you had, I got it through someone else, sir, okay, okay,
absolutely, why, I was negligent in asking  It is not to be done
because the more doubts you people will have, the more you will
not feel like working. This is a good
opportunity, a huge opportunity.
If we can convert this now, then
we will take it forward to the entire pan India
level.
Hi Anshu Chaudhary ji, this is from Sir,
when will the work have to start? So Anshu ji, you
can start the work right now. If you have
not received the ID password, then
connect with Vinod ji once and get
his training and start right now. The
sooner you do it, the better it will be.
You do not have to worry about it. If
anyone has any question or you
people feel that what
problems will arise, what challenges will come
in doing the work, you can also raise that. Please
tell me Sir, is it mandatory to do it at the check post? Is it
not mandatory? You can do it somewhere else too.
That is why I have told you two ways, one is that we will do it at the
check post
with the help of police and the other is that you
are free. Talk to any vehicle in any market
which is not insured.
My insurance is not there, okay, then
you can talk to me.  They will ask Sir, is your car
insured? If it is
not, then Sir, please give me your
RC. I will tell you how much it will cost. What are the
benefits and what are the benefits? I will
tell them all these things.
Why ICICI Bank? They will tell them
because its claim and solvency is the
best. The company is the biggest in the
market and it has the highest trust level.
So, you can tell them all these things.
Yes Sir, if a counter is made there
and at one check post, one ID should be used for both the
works, then is it a good thing or wrong? I could
not understand the meaning of two IDs. Which IDs should I tell you?
Sir, with one ID, one person will be at the check post
and by making a counter, one person will be kept there. It is
possible, but if two people are deputed, then
this means there is coordination between you people. There is nothing
wrong in it.
Yes Sir, it is okay. Look, you have to do the work. You can work from anywhere, from anywhere, in whatever way you do it.
We have no problem with that. Now, whether you
do it by setting up a stall at the square, or by putting up a canopy, you can
work with the police or
So you should go out in the field and work yourself,
whether you work at a petrol pump or a petrol pump, you can
work from anywhere in any way, it is not that
you have to do it this way only, we are giving you a
way from where you
can do it easily, if you have any other good
idea then you can apply that too,
Anshu ji, you are asking how to do it, then there is
a link, your
portal will open from the link, you have to enter the ID and password in it, it is
very simple, okay, and
after that, your training, which vehicle will be
written in it,
this is a two wheeler, select it, fill in whatever needs to be filled in,
after that
you make the payment, it is very simple, this is
your next training, you should note down his number,
Vinod ji, he has shared his number,
you should note down his number in the chat,
once you get the ID and password from him
and enter it in it, Anshu Chaudhary ji, if
you have any question then please tell me, it was
good that you asked the question,
Nitish Kumar ji is saying that sir, this
claim  In how many days will the
claim for what be made? Tee
ji, you can turn on the mic and speak. There is no
problem. What are you
asking about the claim or insurance process?
In how many days will the
policy be made? The policy has not been made yet, so there is no question of a claim.
Yes, tell me Nitish
ji,
okay, you want to know when will the policy
start?
When you get the ID, password and link,
you can start immediately. You
can start right now. Sir,
if you have not received the ID, password and link, then
please
contact Vinod ji after this meeting and get that thing.
Okay Tee
ji, Sir, I will present the screen once. Please
guide me. If
I want to
make a policy through you with your support,
right?
Anshu ji is asking about the support of the police station.
Dharmesh ji will come on the 7th date and he will do
all the liaisoning. Don't worry about that, he will
contact you after doing that.
Whoever is interested will be there.
Hello, yes sir, I want to
share a little screen and I will show you how to make a policy for two minutes
and I have also given the link.  I have
put it in the chat box, please save this link.
You have to enter your ID password, so
sir, please guide me once, I will
try once, if I am
wrong somewhere, then please clear it for me.
My screen is visible to everyone,
you should see in the chat box, you must have received a
message,
this is the link, what did I do, I clicked this link,
this link will go to everyone, please
save this link and keep it.
When I clicked on the link, a
page like this
will open, after the page opens, you will be
asked for username, so whatever username and password you will get,
you have to enter the same ID password,
like the ID password which I have got, I have
shared it with you in Buzz, so I will
see what is my ID password, so
this whole one from IM till
here is my username, that is, ID,
okay, I have pasted it in username
or copied it or typed it
in password, zoom in and
see, if you are not able to see it in your mobile then
zoom in, okay,
I have pasted it, if it is not pasted then
type us DHAR
1990  Okay, in Select Product, you have to
select Retail Product and log in.
As soon as you log in, a
page like this will open. Now you have to do two
wheeler, four wheeler or
private car, the car with white stripe is for
private purposes.
After that, you have PCV which are
commercial vehicles,
passenger carrying vehicles with yellow stripe which are used for carrying passengers,
your T also comes in it, buses
also come in it, all the vehicles running on the road
which are used for carrying passengers, they
come in your PCV
which are goods carriers,
cargo carriers, like Tata S,
that type of vehicles, either dumper type,
truck etc., all of them
come in your GCB which are used for carrying goods.
Suppose I want to insure a two wheeler, then
I have to click on it and
create a new policy. Absolutely new means
for the absolutely new vehicle which is coming out of the agency, either the face details from previous court
already exist, or its
details have to be fetched.  Either
renew existing policy insurance or there
is already insurance of some company
or that insurance has been broken in case
you have to make a new insurance or you have to
renew it, then mostly this will
come, you have to click on it and
click on get nesa quick code, so when
you click here, now you will know
that you have to do full party of that vehicle,
third party, that is, you have to do package
policy, compressive or third party,
full party, compressive package, all three are the same,
you will never get confused,
different words are used at different places, it is possible that
someone may talk to you in any word, then
you should understand that all three
are the same policy which we call full party in our language, so you
see here, you will see an option, if you click on it, then
here you will see, if you have to do four
wheeler full party, then you have to do package, if you have to do
third party, then you have to do TP, if you have to do party, then you have to do package, third party, then you have to do TP,
what do you have to do, suppose you have to do package, full
party, then you have to click on package  If
you click on package, now two
options will appear in it, one will be those vehicles which were
bought before 2019, you do not have to do anything in that, but the
vehicles which were bought after 2019 already have a
third party insurance of five years and
one year on damage, then
its third party insurance will be for five years,
you will add the third party from the date of registration,
you will come to know for how many days the
third party is with it, then what do you have to do,
if suppose only the car or
bus has to be insured, then you should tick yes to the
standalone OD policy which is no here
and if you tick no, then
only the car will be insured and if you tick
no, then both the car and the third
party will be insured, now suppose for example
I have entered the number here,
you people can enter your vehicle number in any chat box, those
whose vehicle is
not insured, put it in the chat box,
through you, through your own vehicle
number, I will tell you all how
easy it is, how quickly the
policy is made,
you can put it in the chat box, you will
not enter anything then  I will enter my vehicle's number,
let me enter my vehicle's number,
I entered UP 63 D
3970, okay, did any number come, okay BR,
this number of Mahavir ji came, after entering you have to click on the click of the click of the click of the click of the click of the click of the click of the click of the click of the click of the click of the click of the click of the click of the click of the click of the click of the click of the click of the click, it is telling that
the policy is future dated, means this is the third party already issued policy on damage, okay, so you can enter it, see the complete details have come, from which RTO, which vehicle is this, what is its model, when was it purchased, when did its first R10 start, you enter the policy date,
then after that, the details of your
previous policy of the vehicle,
when is it expiring, you have to
enter the expiry date on 'y', okay,
which company's policy was it,
which vehicle's policy was it last year, suppose we
entered Bajaj's, then it will ask you to enter the policy number, so
we enter the national number on 'y',
I am telling you this, you should not do this, you have to
enter the correct details, if you enter any wrong details then there will be a
problem for you and the customer,
You have to enter this detail correctly, this is being done just
to explain to you, yes see
old
or here you have to enter the policy number,
now it will ask whether there is any claim on your vehicle last year or
this year, that is, have you taken the claim or
not, if you have taken a claim then you have to say yes
on this, if you have not taken a claim then you have to say no, keep
this in mind that if you have taken a claim
and you say no, then it is possible that if a
claim comes on the vehicle in future then you will not
get the claim and the MC will also be recovered from the customer,
so pay close attention to this, do
not make any mistake in this, you must ask the customer,
if he says yes or no, whatever he says has to be
entered, then how much was there in the policy last year, you have to
enter as much NCB as there was in the policy last year, if there was
no policy last year then it does not matter, you enter yes
here, okay, then
NCV will
not be asked from you, okay, policy start
date, third policy start date, that is, third
party, your policy which is
4124, when was the vehicle purchased after the policy start, on
18th December 2020, so here you do
not have to enter the date which is in your policy  The date of the
third party will be there, that has to be entered, I am doing this just to
tell you and explain,
so 188 2020 here we have to select
August 2020, okay, so the third party
is clear till 2025, now we have to get the quote, as if
we get the quote, we have got the quotation of
838 for car insurance on damage, in
which you can see what all is there, on
damage is 710 and GST is 128, total
838, now if the customer says that I want to take PA cover as well
or zero dep, then you
see here, click here below to customize the
coverage, you have to click on it,
what all do you want, do you want zero dep,
click on zero dep,
okay and what covers do you want,
I think only one cover is right for you,
you recalculate, then you will know
how much, in 1173 173, you will get the full EBITDA of your car, that is, EBITDA of the
car with zero dep, you will already get the
third party cover.  Now
suppose you have to send a quotation to a customer, then
you see here where it is
written 1173 sir, above it the premium
breakup is written, you click on it
and after clicking it it says send link,
you click on send link then it will ask for the
customer's mobile number, now you enter the customer's
mobile number, his customer
number like 89 56 42
95 24 I have entered my number, okay
now enter the customer's email ID,
you can enter yours in CC so that you also get to
know that the link has come, in case it does
not reach the customer, his mail may be wrong,
so you can copy it from your side and
paste it and send it,
as soon as I submit it, the
link will go to the customer in which he will get the complete premium
breakup, his quotation,
how much is the premium of our vehicle,
what covers are we getting, what are the
benefits, from when till when, he can check the complete details,
he has a vehicle,
whatever is the vehicle number, is it correct or not,
he will get all these things now, suppose  Take it,
if the buyer says yes I
want to do the policy then you have to come and click on buy now.
After clicking on buy now, now
you have to check whether both the invoice numbers are correct or not.
You have to match them with the RC.
Whatever number is in the RC with the policy copy, if it is correct then it
is fine, if it is wrong then you have to correct it on 'y'. The
number which will be in the RC has to be done with the same number.
Now the message that has been sent to us,
brother, please tell us your PAN number.
Who is Mankus Kumar? First number
Mahavir Kumar Mahavir Kumar. If you have the PAN
number, then pay attention, when you do the customer's
policy, then take the Aadhar card and PAN
card of the person in whose name the
RC
will be. Okay, because doing KYC
is compulsory, you cannot do the policy without KYC,
so you will have to do the KYC
here. You will have to enter the PAN number of the
person. Suppose you enter the wrong PAN
number, then the policy will not be made in his name
and you should not do this either. If you do
this then you will incur loss
and the customer will leave you, otherwise
you should not make any mistake in the PAN number like the
customer's  So, in place of customer,
suppose I am the customer, I am
entering my name, but you don't have to
enter yours, just to show, to
explain to you, what happens,
EJNPK 1344D, now you will come to know whether
I am doing it right or wrong, right,
I am entering some wrong details,
okay, I have submitted, now when I submit it,
you will come to know what it is,
my name is Vinod Kumar, that is,
my details have been taken, now in the policy,
instead of his name, the policy will be made in my name, a
joke policy, then it will be of no use to you, the
customer, so you have to keep this thing in
mind that you have to enter only the customer's details, you
have to do the customer's KYC, then
you will enter the details here, submit his PIN
number details, the complete details will come,
you have to proceed, okay, the
complete details have come, now you will click on create proposal,
as soon as you click on create proposal, then
see below, the payment link is
visible, you have to click on send link, you
can also click on send link or you can also click on pay now
and  When you click on Pay Now,
UPI Wallet Insta will appear, so if you click on send link, then the
link will go to him and if
you think that you do not want to send the link, for example,
phone pay, then you do
not have to do anything, you have to click on UPI,
this type of page will open, it will appear to
scan the QR code, tell him to
scan it and make the payment, this is one method,
second UPI mobile number, like
my number works in phone pay, 7897 82
9792, okay @
Wabi, in this way you have to enter the customer's mobile number
and his UPI ID, you have to
enter the UPI ID directly and make the Pay Now,
now a link will come on my phone
in the notification, I will open it, it has come to
me, I will open it
and make the payment, as soon as I
make the payment, my policy will be created, it is a very
easy process, there is
no need to think much in this, but
you have to enter the details absolutely correct, if
you enter the wrong details then there will be a problem
and we do not want you to enter any wrong details,
okay, so this process is done now
after that  Where will you see the policy you have made?
You have to click on ICICI Lombard.
You have come here. Whatever policies you have
made, you will click on the policy of the
forer killer and then
click on get policy page. For all the policies
you have made, the date will be pending payment as on today's date. If you click on get
policy, then the details will come here.
How much is the pending payment? Okay, save it.
Whatever proposal you have saved or the
payment link has been opened. You will get that detail here.
My quote. Whatever quote you have made till now
is fine. Like right now I have
made a quote of BR 39, this one is visible as of today's date. You can
forward it.
Okay, these things will be available to you
and then after that you have to do the forer TP in the same way.
Sir, it was clear till now, I think
I clarified it. If somewhere in
between, no, it was absolutely correct. If someone is asking in the chat, can you
take cash? No,
you should not take it at all. You should not take cash under any circumstances.
If you do it yourself or
from someone, you have to take online payment and
because he  A lot of problems will arise from this, you should
never take cash, you will
also get trapped in it and if his policy gets cancelled or anything happens then he will
not be able to get his money back,
okay, so that is not to be done, you have to take
care of this thing immediately, do
not take cash,
rest you have been given an ID password for training
purpose, you can enter it and use it, rest I will give
you your ID password, you can take your
ID pass,
you can use this training ID password for learning,
Naveen ji, if you want to ask something, you can do it,
yes sir, yes
sir, all three policies are fail, first party,
second party, third party, so all three policies
together, you can do it, first of all
understand the
meaning of first party, you should understand what people get
confused about, right, there is no second party, there is
full party and third
party, there is full party, right,
who is the first party who
gives the payment, yes, that is, if you get
your policy made, you will give the money, then you are the
first party, the second party is the
insurance company which takes the money, okay,
third party  It is the person who is walking on the road,
whom we don't even know, sir,
or for whom you are preparing to save yourself,
and I was asking this, sir, like if the bike is
insured, then suppose it is
my bike, then the bike is insured
and my own insurance will also be covered
in it, if you take the cover, then the
driver is also covered, if that driver
is the owner, if both the owner and the driver are the same, then he has a
cover of 15 lakhs, ha ha,
this is what I was asking, sir,
Jilo Tiwari ji from Darbhanga is asking, what will you do if
he doesn't have the facility of online payment, then wo
n't we, Manu
Tiwari
ji, it is his job to make the arrangement,
yes, take cash, you will get into trouble,
depositing it and making the transaction from your account,
that
means it will become very difficult for you later on,
sorry, no, no, there is no problem, it is
important to ask, there should be no shortage in asking, there should be no
shortage in asking, if you ask the right question, you will
get the right answer, you should not worry, that is why it is being
said that it is not to be done, okay,
Naveen ji, tell me, you should continue, are you saying something  I had
a question
Sir, hello yes please tell me, I was saying that
if by the way
if the ID password of some person is
found and by Dave his brother
goes somewhere for 2-4-10 days then the network of that ID is
bad, please keep connecting,
hello ok 367 yes ok Naveen ji
I am talking about you and if you have any question then
you can go to the chat box,
hello Naveen ji,
you will face problem in that, if you correct the wrong number, then there is
no problem, if you do something wrong
then you will start facing problem, if you
find out that the number of the car is 49 41, then you
enter 4 42, then
what will happen, it will take
next three days to get it changed, ok oh it will take a week, then
what will happen, what kind of a
person is he, he messed up everything for me,
if he does it properly then it is fine, if he
messes up then what happens is that the
head of the family is responsible for everything,
but the problem will increase and the change will happen, there is
no problem, it will change but there will be
problem  By the time it comes, it will make your life hell in a day,
whose mistake you will make, you were
asking me, so there is no
problem, okay, thank you sir, you do
n't have any more questions about
[sangeet],
okay, then this has
got a conclusion, call Vinod ji once
or message him and take all his things,
okay, what else are you
asking,
Mahavir ji is asking, sir, is the work limited
or unlimited,
Mahavir ji, there is no limit in this,
how much can you do, see this
incentive, the more you will get, ask, ask,
Mahavir ji, you have raised your hand,
hello, Mahavir ji,
tell me, sir, you were asking, like this work means, it is
unlimited for 10 years,
after 10 years, your ID is defused,
you cannot work, no, it will not be like that,
if there is a problem, then
another ID will go in its place, no problem, it means
it is not fixed, you can leave it after 10 years, no, no, it is not like this, it is not like this, as
long as you keep taking insurance of the vehicle
and accordingly your ID will keep getting made, there is no problem in
that
No problem okay sir okay Mahavir ji from Piya you are
from Purnia where from Purnia Rupali
Parkhand okay from Lee okay okay sir okay after
talking to Vinod ji and you guys starting from today
we have a one and a half hour trip today
all of you please accept your ID and password
okay I haven't even created the ID and password yet our
message
also you might not have received it due to some things that are going on
you guys will get
everything before the due date
and then some training will be required so we will
train again okay
and we have to try to do solid work do
n't do it in a paper form work that is of a
problematic form anything if you don't understand then
please
ask again one person is asking the same question Mr.
Choudhary ji how will we get our money okay it will come
in your account whatever is there will
come in your account so do
n't worry about that Vinod ji
and
Dharmesh people will keep all your accounts
and as soon as you earn whatever money you have, they will
send it to you don't have to worry
and instead of doing this you guys do whatever is there,
Ansura  Yes, he will also tell you
how much incentive there is for every vehicle, different incentive for
two wheeler, different for four wheeler,
different for truck, everyone has it but there is a very
good incentive, you do
n't have to worry about that, it will be more than your salary,
if you work properly then it will be
more than your salary,
you guys keep a note of all the questions, okay and
after that when the need arises,
we will connect you once again and after connecting we will
answer all your questions,
what should you guys do before this, first of all
get your ID password, get training
so that when the work comes in front then it does not happen
that I do not know anything because there will be
many people in one location, only those who are good will be
promoted,
they will be brought forward, okay
sir, now with the ID password that we will get, we
can do our job,
absolutely we can do it, absolutely we can do it, yes
sir, you start with your vehicle, everyone should
start with their own vehicle,
okay, then we will end the session, if you have any other
question,
please message Vinod ji.
Tell me if you want to tell me,
tell Sachin ji, let's
go from there, I have given the number for the location,
if there is any problem then you can contact us, the
number is given in it, for Purnia, appoint a
location and team leader who
has all the information so that all that can be
taken by talking to them, Mur Sudhanshu
is there, I have made that, I got a call, we will
appoint a main leader from different districts, they will keep the
report of the group and they will
send it to us and everyone will have their own
separate number for different districts in
which we will keep adding you,
Manohar ji is asking where is the number,
go a little up, Manohar ji, Sachin ji's
number is written in the name of Sachin Singh,
by the way Sachin, please enter your number once again,
sir, who is the in-charge of Samastipur,
right now I am the one
from Samastipur, wait
a minute,
sir, I have also entered my number, all of you please
save the number, try it when needed,
rest of you all keep my number with you, those
who have not got the ID password,
please text me on this number, I will be there
What will you enter, your name, district name
and write below Sir, I need ID and password, just
send this much by messaging, hardly
within 35 to 40 minutes you will get the ID and password, there will be an
automatic reply,
okay,
I have also
shared my contact details, if
anyone from here has any confusion, you
can talk, no problem, okay, so
let's do this, let's end the session, okay,
and then contact, okay, okay, let's
end this, and you
guys are completely ready, those who have
not received the ID and password, message us,
you will get the ID and password, and
after getting the password, then you can
start your work from today itself,
okay, okay, thank you sir,
still you
guys